<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Corvus</string>

    <string name="facebook_app_id">484097268816754</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb484097268816754</string>
    <string name="title_activity_collection_add">CollectionAdd</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home_page">HomePage</string>
    <string name="title_activity_coin_list">CoinList</string>
    <string name="title_activity_test_expanded_collection">TestExpandedCollection</string>
    <string name="test_banner_ad">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>
    <string name="test_interstitial_ad">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/1033173712</string>

    <string name="coinlist_interstitial_ad">ca-app-pub-1744081621312112/9425905671</string>
    <string name="refcollections_interstitial_ad">ca-app-pub-1744081621312112/9675411014</string>
    <string name="refcoinlist_interstitial_ad">ca-app-pub-1744081621312112/9481745995</string>


    <string name="test_reward_ad">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/5224354917</string>

    <!-- For FAQ & one time dialogs -->

    <string name="universal_01">You can access this information from the FAQ available through the drop down menus in most screens.</string>

    <string name="login_01">Your collection will be stored in the cloud to minimize the resource requirements of your device. We need a unique, verifiable ID to authenticate your access.</string>
    <string name="login_02">Corvus is only accessing your email, which is necessary for authentication, and your user ID.</string>

    <string name="homepage_01">You need at least one collection to enter coins. You can set up as many as you need.</string>
    <string name="homepage_02">Currently, Corvus has one level for sub-dividing your overall collection.</string>
    <string name="homepage_03">Click a collection card to access coins in the collection or long-click to view, edit or delete the collection itself.</string>
    <string name="homepage_04">The reference collections accessible from the drop down menu on most screens show how we thought of setting up collections to maximize Corvus.</string>

    <string name="collectionadd_01">You only need to enter a collection name to set up a collection.</string>
    <string name="collectionadd_02">You can upload any PNG or JPG picture from your device gallery to represent your collection; best results when cropped square.</string>
    <string name="collectionadd_03">We are working on making data input easier including uploading pictures from your computer and batch uploads from excel.</string>
    <string name="collectionadd_04">You can enter a unique numeric ID for your collection. You will be able to sort your collections on this ID as well as on other factors such us last update time and collection value.</string>
    <string name="collectionadd_05">Your data is safe. Only you can access your collection and we backup our entire database daily.</string>
    <string name="collectionadd_06">You can enter one standard reference (for example the RIC, RSC, RPC, ERIC, etc.) You will able to sort your coins on that reference number. You can add other attribution references in the Notes section as you wish.</string>


    <string name="refcollections_01">The reference collections are there to help you attribute and describe coins.</string>
    <string name="refcollections_02">We are working on search capabilities for Corvus. For now we have divided the reference collection into digestable chunks that follow the RIC and which you can easily scroll through.</string>
    <string name="refcollections_03">The Corvus reference collections have over 10,000 coins all vf+ or better. We continue to upload them to the app daily.</string>
    <string name="refcollections_04">Yes!! We are working on automating collection sharing. For now you can send us an email letting us know you wish to share and we can add your coins to our reference libraries. We will indicate them as belonging to you or not as per your instructions.</string>
    <string name="refcollections_05">Coin values are tricky and volatile. For each reference coin we put all the pricing information we know about the actual coin in the provenance field. Sometimes it is dated and comes in several currencies. We also take a stab at our view of the coin\'s worth today in the value field but that is our opinion only.</string>


    <string name="coinadd_01">You can add as many coins to your collection as you wish. For easier viewing consider setting up multiple collections where you can group similar coins.</string>
    <string name="coinadd_02">Only the Personage field is mandatory. We strongly suggest using the attribution field to make it easy to sort your collection.</string>
    <string name="coinadd_03">You can upload any PNG or JPG picture of your coin from your device gallery; best results when cropped to a rectangle with the coin edges close to the image edge.</string>
    <string name="coinadd_04">The fields you do not fill in will not appear at all in your record to make viewing easier. </string>
    <string name="coinadd_05">Corvus allows you to sort your coins on the standard reference number which must be numeric. In the [Reference]var field you can put in qualifiers such as letters, variants, etc.</string>
    <string name="coinadd_06">Corvus is not yet optimized for Provincial coins. We are working on adding greek alphabet capabilities to the app.</string>

    <string name="coinlist_01">Click the floating button at the bottom of the screen to add a single coin. You can also replicate an existing coin from your collection or from a CORVUS reference collection. See the REPLICATE FAQ.</string>
    <string name="coinlist_02">You can mass upload coin information from a spreadsheet except for images which have to be added manually to each record after. See the MASS UPLOAD FAQ below</string>
    <string name="coinlist_03">Click on a coin-card to show all the information about the coin. Swipe right or left to delete the coin. Longclick to modify the coin record.</string>
    <string name="coinlist_04">You can sort the coins on the personage, RIC number or last-modified. Sort options are in the drop down menu.</string>
    <string name="coinlist_05">We are working on adding search capabilities to Corvus.</string>
    <string name="coinlist_06"></string>

    <!-- END OF FAQ & one time dialogs -->
    <string name="title_activity_ref_collections">RefCollections</string>
    <string name="title_activity_ref_coin_list">RefCoinList</string>
    <string name="title_activity_coin_add">CoinAdd</string>
    <string name="title_activity_excel">Excel</string>
    <string name="title_activity_ref_collections_dir">RefCollectionsDir</string>


</resources>
