<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Corvus</string>

    <string name="facebook_app_id">436089210504491</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb436089210504491</string>
    <string name="title_activity_collection_add">CollectionAdd</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home_page">HomePage</string>
    <string name="title_activity_coin_list">CoinList</string>
    <string name="title_activity_test_expanded_collection">TestExpandedCollection</string>

    <!-- For FAQ & one time dialogs -->

    <string name="universal_01">You can always access this information from the FAQ available through the drop down menus in most screens.</string>

    <string name="login_01">Your collection will be stored in the cloud to minimize the storage and memory requirements of your device. We need a unique, verifiable ID to authenticate your access.</string>
    <string name="login_02">Corvus is only accessing your email which is necessary for authentication and your user ID.</string>

    <string name="homepage_01">You need at least one collection to enter coins. You can set up as many as you need.</string>
    <string name="homepage_02">Currently, Corvus has only this level to split your overall collection into sub-collections.</string>
    <string name="homepage_03">Click a collection card to access coins in the collection or long-click to view, edit or delete the collection itself.</string>
    <string name="homepage_04">The reference collections can to help you identify coins and demonstrate our view of how to maximize Corvus functionality.</string>
    <string name="homepage_05">Currently, Corvus doesn\'t automate identification but you can key-word search both your own and reference collections.</string>

    <string name="collectionadd_01">You only need to enter a collection name to set up a collection.</string>
    <string name="collectionadd_02">You can upload any PNG or JPG picture to represent your collection; best results when cropped square.</string>
    <string name="collectionadd_03">We are working on making data input easier including uploading pictures from your computer and batch uploads from excel.</string>
    <string name="collectionadd_04">Your data is safe. Only you can access your collection and we backup our entire database daily.</string>
    <string name="collectionadd_05">.</string>

</resources>
